cashedge.com 2007-04-12

# CashEdge

Your privacy and security are of the utmost importance to CashEdge, and we are committed to safeguarding any information that you share with us. In order to provide our Services, we must obtain certain personal information from you regarding your accounts and financial relationships. Our pledge is to keep this information secure and to use it only as you so authorize. 

**The Personal Information CashEdge collects** : 

  * CashEdge does not gather any personal information if you are merely visiting our Web site. You can visit our site, read about our products and services without having to volunteer any information about yourself. 
  * CashEdge only requests your personal and financial information at the time that you register to use our aggregation and funds transfer services, in which case you will be asked to provide the following: 
    1. User ID and a Password that you create. 
    2. First and last names, addresses and e-mail account information. 
    3. Basic security-related data such as social security number, date of birth, city of birth and mother’s maiden name. 

Your user profile information will allow us to authenticate and verify your identity so that you may indeed create an account with us to use our services. 

_We collect only such information as you knowingly provide to us or specifically authorize us to obtain on your behalf._

  * CashEdge’s technology allows you to aggregate financial information and allows you to transfer funds from bank, brokerages and other accounts that you maintain with various financial institutions. In order to provide such services, it is necessary for CashEdge to access your third party accounts at financial institutions on your behalf. To enable this access, you will need to provide us with all such information that is required by your financial institution, such as bank account numbers. We will use this information only on your behalf, to access your third party accounts and to carry out your instructions. Please know that when you provide us with your financial institution passwords, this information is completely encrypted in a manner that makes the actual password inaccessible to CashEdge, its employees and any third parties. Currently, the CashEdge funds transfer service is available only in the United States. CashEdge stores your personal information on a secure server based in the United States of America. 

**How CashEdge uses Your Information and who has access to it:**

  * CashEdge uses your personal information to provide you with our services, to notify you of any product updates, and changes to our user policies. 
  * CashEdge does not sell or exchange any personally identifiable financial or otherwise information, or account login information to any (i.e. non-affiliate of CashEdge) third party. With an affiliated party we may share your personally identifiable information, including verifying your identity with and confirming that you own the accounts at the specific banks and financial institutions from which you choose to “aggregate” your accounts or transfer funds. We may also, in the necessary course of delivering our services, and for internal risk management purposes (for example to confirm that you have sufficient funds to support substantial money transfers), share personally identifiable information with an intended partner to authenticate the information that you have supplied. 
  * If you do not agree to the sharing of information per the aforesaid, we recommend that you do not sign-up for our services. 
  * CashEdge does reserve the right to share anonymous, non-individualized and identity-blind aggregated data. 
  * CashEdge also reserves the right to disclose or report personally identifiable information as permitted by law (for example, if CashEdge has a “good faith belief” that it is required to do so in order to (i) comply with applicable law or with legal process (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of CashEdge; (iii) enforce the terms of this Policy or CashEdge’s User Agreement, etc). 
  * CashEdge will for the purpose of address and credit verification and risk management where it is necessary, exchange information with credit reporting agencies, reputable reference sources and clearinghouse services. 
  * CashEdge-authorized employees and customer service representatives will access your personal and financial information only when necessary to comply with your requests, maintain your accounts, or otherwise meet your needs. To keep your information secure, we require that all of our employees sign strict confidentiality agreements. Access to sensitive customer information such as customer bank balances and transaction details, is highly restricted and is limited to only authorized employees. 
  * We treat information concerning our former customers the same way we treat information about our current customers. 

**Choices Customers have:**

  * CashEdge will keep your personal and account information accurate and up to date. You can access, review and update your personal information at any time by clicking on **“Profile”**. You will not be able to make changes to your third party accounts at financial institutions through CashEdge. For any problems or to update your Profile you can notify us at [privacy@CashEdge.com](mailto:privacy@cashedge.com).   

  * If you wish to discontinue your use of the services, you can unsubscribe at any time by clicking on the "Unsubscribe From Service Feature" from the Profile Tab or, by writing at CashEdge Inc., 2841 Junction Ave, Suite 101, San Jose, CA 95134-1921. 

**Security Measures that CashEdge has put in place to protect your information:**

  * CashEdge has multiple levels of security, designed especially by us. In that we take every precaution to protect your information, when you submit sensitive information, that information is encrypted and protected with the strongest encryption software available. Your information is protected both online and off-line using technologic and physical measures. For information on the specifics of our Security Architecture, please see CashEdge's Security Policy. 
  * The use of “ Cookies” is an industry standard that refers to pieces of information that a Web site transfers to your computer’s hard disk for record keeping purposes. By storing information about your preferences on a particular site, many major Web sites use cookies to provide useful features for their customers. In our case we use “Cookies” to maintain session information for logged in members and to prevent the need for re-entry of login information. The “Cookies” used by CashEdge are present only when you are in session- they are deleted when you log off. CashEdge does not use “persistent” cookies (that is, cookies that remain after you log off) to store any personal information on a browser. If you attempt to disable the session cookies you will no longer be able to access the CashEdge service. 
  * CashEdge places your personal and financial information on a secure portion of our Web site. Your CashEdge login name is always encrypted. Your CashEdge Password is one-way encrypted (this type of encryption prevents us from deciphering your CashEdge password). Your Financial Institution User IDs and Passwords are encrypted using your CashEdge password (this means that until you log in to CashEdge and provide us with your password, CashEdge cannot decrypt the User ID and Password for your third party accounts). Neither our software, nor that of our employees can decode this information at any time. 
  * Your CashEdge password is your private key into your account. You must never share it with anyone and you should change it periodically. You can change your password at any time by clicking on **“Profile”**. PLEASE REMEMBER that if you forget your password, we can reset your CashEdge account, but you will have to re-enter your User ID's and Passwords for financial institutions, as we do not have access to this information. 
  * After you have finished accessing your CashEdge account, please remember to log off. This prevents someone else from accessing your account. ****
  * To preserve your privacy, you will be logged off automatically when you have been inactive for a period of time. For secure access to your private information, you will need to log on again. For security reasons you will be denied access to your account after 3 unsuccessful log in attempts. ****

**Third Party Sites**

  * The CashEdge Web site contains links to other Web sites. Such links are provided solely as a convenience to you. CashEdge does not endorse any products or services offered on those sites and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. CashEdge is not responsible for the personal and financial information that you provide such parties. 

The information and materials contained in these pages are subject to change. You can review this policy and any updates at any time by going to the Privacy Policy. If at some point in the future there is a change to our information usage practices that affect your personally identifiable information, we will notify you by email of the relevant changes. Regardless of later updates, we will never use the information you submit under this current policy in a new way without first providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prevent that use. You can choose to opt-out at any time by notifying us either by writing to us at CashEdge, Inc., 2841 Junction Ave, Suite 101, San Jose, CA 95134-1921. Or by sending us e-mail at [privacy@CashEdge.com](mailto:privacy@cashedge.com). 

By participating in the BBBOnLine and TRUSTe Privacy Program, we have made a commitment to meet these programs’ strict requirements regarding how we treat your personal and financial information. 

CashEdge has been certified by TRUSTe, Thawte, and BBBOnLine to help promote the principles of disclosure and informed consent on the Internet. In providing our services to you we abide by the EU Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the Department of Commerce regarding collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union. 

Further information about BBBOnLine, TRUSTe and Thawte is available at [www.bbbonline.org](http://www.bbbonline.org/), [www.TRUSTe.org](http://www.truste.org/) and [www.thawte.com](http://www.thawte.com/)

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Privacy Questions, CashEdge Inc., 2841 Junction Ave, Suite 101, San Jose, CA 95134-1921 Or [privacy@CashEdge.com](mailto:privacy@CashEdge.com). If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry is not satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe through the [TRUSTe Watchdog Dispute Resolution Process (http://truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php)](http://truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php). TRUSTe will serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns. 

Back to Homepage

[  
](http://www.bbbonline.org/cks.asp?id=7102000115631)
